A Finding Aid to the Harry Siddons Mowbray and Mowbray Family Papers, 1872-1976, in the Archives of American Art aaa.mowbharr
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1874-circa 1928; Series 9; 4.7 Linear feet Box 4-14, 17-18
  - Works of Art (Box 5)
    - Prudential Life Insurance Mural, Neward, NJ, circa 1920 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Madison Square Church, New York City, NY, circa 1920 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Reference Photos, Works of Art by Others, circa 1900 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Oversized material housed in OV17-18. 7 glass plate negatives; Housed in box 11
  - Lantern Slides of Works of Art, circa 1900-1928 (Box 6-10)
  - Glass Plate Negatives of Works of Art, circa 1900-1928; 68 Glass negatives (Box 11-12)
  - Oversized Photo Album, 1890-1914 (Box 13)
    Material from Box 4, F15
  - Oversized Photographs of Works of Art, circa 1910 (Box 14)
    Material from Box 5, F4
  - Oversized Photographs, Reference, circa 1910 (Box 17-18)
    Material from Box 5, F14
- Scrapbooks, circa 1890-1920; Series 10; 0.3 Linear feet Box 5, 13-15
  This series consists of three scrapbooks, two of which were compiled by Harry Siddons Mowbray and the other likely compiled by George Mowbray. One scrapbook by Harry Siddons Mowbray contains clippings and some printed material, photographs, and invitations relating to his time spent in Rome with the American Academy in Rome. The other scrapbook by Mowbray contains clippings relating to his career and artworks. The George Mowbray scrapbook contains clippings concerning his chemical inventions.
  - American Academy in Rome Scrapbook, Compiled by Harry Siddons Mowbray, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, Compiled by Harry Siddons Mowbray, circa 1890-1920s (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Oversized material housed in Box 14
  - Clippings Scrapbook, Compiled by George Mowbray, circa 1900-1920 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Oversized items housed in Box 14
  - Oversized Scrapbooks, circa 1890-1914 (Box 13-14)
    Material from Box 13, F15-17
- Artwork, 1870-1910; Series 11; 3 Folders Box 5, 13
  This series contains scattered prints, etchings, and sketches by Harry Siddons Mowbray and others. There is also a photocopy of a booklet illustrated by Mowbray relating to the history of England.
  - Prints and Etchings, by Harry Siddons Mowbray, circa 1880-1910 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sketches, by Harry Siddons Mowbray and Others, circa 1870-1900 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Photocopy of History of England, Illustrated Booklet by Harry Siddons Mowbray, 1876 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oversized Sketches, circa 1900 (Box 13)
    Material from Box 5, F19